









# CONTACTS



Cheboksary, Russia



+7 999 199 05 90



ru9art@gmail.com

## **ABOUT ME**

I have experience with React, Redux, TypeScript as the main stack, and I want to develop in this direction.

Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies.

I'm planning to study Node.js, because my next focus is to become a Full-Stack Developer. And also I have interest to design.

#### **SKILLS**

- React, Redux, Thunk, Saga
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- HTTPS, RestAPI, Axios
- React Native
- Styled Component, SCSS
- Unit Tests Jest
- Material UI, Ant Design
- TDD, Jest, Storybook
- Git, Jira
- HTML5, CSS3

# **LANGUAGES**

- English -
- Russian Native

# **VLADISLAV** MUZYKA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

REELANCE / TEAM WORK | Jan 2021 - PRESENT

- Project architectural solutions (layering UI, BLL, DAL)
- Create functional and technical application documents
- Added new functionality in accordance with the new endpoints (REST) on the back-end, namely login, registration, password recovery, password reset.
  - I used React Form, Formik, Formact, useForm.
  - During the development process, I wrote tests for the reducer (TDD) using Jest.
  - Translated the application to the Redux Toolkit to set a clear and understandable flow and simplify debugging in the future.
  - Fixed bugs related to side effects (using React .memo, useCallback, useEffect cleanup)

#### Dodo Pizza

SHIFT MANAGER | Feb 2016 - Dec 2020

- Execution of directors' orders
- Communication with the customer, solving the problems that have
- Scheduling the shift of all employees
- Management of employees, delegation of tasks, control of the processes of preparation of products and delivery to customers
- Ordering products, equipment, consumables

## My Hobby

Feb 2012 - Feb 2018

- Website development on CMS WordPress, DLE, Joomla
- Development of a game server on a linux VPS/VDS system
- Writing simple plugins on the Pawn language

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

# **IT-INCUBATOR**

Front-End developer (React, Redux, TypeScript) | 2021

• Work with React, Redux, TypeScript, Promise, REST API, GIT, immutable.js, Heroku, Material UI, Ant Design, StoryBook, TDD

#### **HTML-ACADEMY**

Front-End | Aug 2020 - Jan 2021

Basic course on HTML5. CSS3, JavaScript











# CONTACTS



Cheboksary, Russia



+7 999 199 05 90



ru9art@gmail.com

# **ABOUT ME**

I have experience with React, Redux, TypeScript as the main stack, and I want to develop in this direction.

Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies.

I'm planning to study Node.js, because my next focus is to become a Full-Stack Developer. And also I have interest to design.

#### **SKILLS**

- React, Redux, Thunk, Saga
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- HTTPS, RestAPI, Axios
- React Native
- Styled Component, SCSS
- Unit Tests Jest
- Material UI, Ant Design
- TDD, Jest, Storybook
- Git, Jira
- HTML5, CSS3

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English -
- Russian Native

# **VLADISLAV** MUZYKA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

REELANCE / TEAM WORK | Jan 2021 - PRESENT

- Project architectural solutions (layering UI, BLL, DAL)
- Create functional and technical application documents
- Added new functionality in accordance with the new endpoints (REST) on the back-end, namely login, registration, password recovery, password reset.
  - I used React Form, Formik, Formact, useForm.
  - During the development process, I wrote tests for the reducer (TDD) using Jest.
  - Translated the application to the Redux Toolkit to set a clear and understandable flow and simplify debugging in the future.
  - Fixed bugs related to side effects (using React .memo, useCallback, useEffect cleanup)

#### Dodo Pizza

SHIFT MANAGER | Feb 2016 - Dec 2020

- Выполнение распоряжений директоров
- Общение с заказчиком, решение возникших проблем
- Составление графика смены всех работников
- Управление сотрудниками, делегирование задач, контроль процессов приготоволени продуктов и доставки клиетам
- Заказ продукции, оборудования, расходных материалов

# My Hobby

Feb 2012 - Feb 2018

- Website development on CMS WordPress, DLE, Joomla
- Development of a game server on a linux VPS/VDS system
- Writing simple plugins on the Pawn language

# **EDUCATION HISTORY**

### **IT-INCUBATOR**

Front-End developer (React, Redux, TypeScript) | 2021

• Work with React, Redux, TypeScript, Promise, REST API, GIT, immutable.js, Heroku, Material UI, Ant Design, StoryBook, TDD

# **HTML-ACADEMY**

Front-End | Aug 2020 - Jan 2021

Basic course on HTML5. CSS3, JavaScript